Translation: astrogirl, Corrections: shuushuuma
Corrections, Ajustments and Fixes:
CEbbinghaus (with help from honeybrie)
www.subtitles.de
Life is so sad,
I have no one to kiss,
love is not easy,
but I don't want to miss.
Out of this world
I will fly to the moon,
find me somebody
Area 51
to hug and kiss me soon.
(Secret US Military Base)
Find me somebody
22. July 2004
to hug and kiss me soon.
- Was the White House informed?
- No. Too Risky.
The President Is amidst an election campaign.
Don't let it slip! It would
provoke a global mass hysteria.
- We imposed a gag order.
- Does the Pentagon think it's dangerous?
General, I commend Defcon 2.
Be careful, Sir.
Oh my God!
Watcha lookin' at?
(300 years later)
(Regulator) Once upon a time our
ancestors came from Earth to colonize Mars.
Today we return to Earth...
to once and for all
annilihate its pathetic inhabitants!
Jens, my trusty disciple,
our vision has come true.
Earth belongs us now!
Queen Metapha, we are defenseless.
The attack met us unprepared.
Our fleet has been destroyed.
- How can that be?
- They deciphered our shield access codes!
They can even
bug our local calls.
Mars makes you mobile
- Majesty, we must surrender!
- Oh no, you cannot do that!
forgive me.
Those Martians came
down upon us like grasshoppers.
Their troops are stationed
all around the globe
But we can't just stick
our sand in the head
in two hours at the latest the Mars Regulator
will be sitting on your throne!
we have already lost
- There could be one last chance.
- What do you mean?
Time travel.
(whispers) The sideffects are unjustifiable.
- But time travel is prohibited!
I think we can bend the rules a little.
Please go on.
We must travel back in time
and prevent the colonization of Mars.
- Only so can we prevent this war.
- Absurd! We don't even know
whether time travel is safe for humans.
We've never tested it.
- And who would be able to do this?
- I was thinking of...
- the Surprise crew!
- Oh Goodness! Why those of all people!
'Cause we're so pretty and so smart
and so slim and so slender
We'll be Miss Waikiki!
And shower to the left!
And shower to the right!
And don't forget the soap!
One more time!
And five, six, seven, eight
Five, six, seven, eight
And touch and push!
And towel to the left!
And towel to the right!
And don't forget the willy!
Dry the willy to the beat!
- You cannot be serious!
- We have no other choice
They are mankind's last hope.
Or are there any volunteers?
So basically you are saying
that the salvation of Earth
Depends on this crew of all things
If you put it that way, senator Eric...
Yes!
We have no idea where they are.
No word from them in years!
We will just have to find them then
there they are!
I can't believe it
How could they veer off course this far?
Contact them immediately!
- There are in the middle of nowhere!
- Are you really surprised?.
Captain's log no. 1 of our
Traumschiff Surprise, Captain Kork.
It's way too chilly for this stardate.
All 40 men of my crew are in good health.
Only two have a slight cold.
Gunther has blackboard duty for this week.
I am worried that in five months from now
we'll run out of stamps.
We have got to do something about that.
But not right now.
Today we have our yearly health check
before the summer holidays start.
Looking forward to having
my temperature taken.
if all is fine, I'll have a nice Schnitzel
with french fries and ketchup,
a small mixed salad and
to drink a large spezi.
- The same fagging every year!
- The Honolulu bathing season starts in two weeks!
You'll need a flawless waistline
if you want to be Miss Waikiki!
Constantly does my back in though.
Since when do vulcanettes
even have a spine?
- None of yours, you dumb cow!
- He's not even a purebred Vulcanette.
- Oh, I am!
- No, you're a mutt!
Gasp
I am a Vulcanette Vulgaris.
We can be up to 400 years old because we are
a type of Galapagos turtle!
- And what are you?
- I'm the captain.
- You just screwed your way up!
- So what's so bad about that?
Galapagos turtle!
That's why you're so slow!
and you have a baboon's ass!
My oh my
(All) So?
- Your values are disastrous, as always.
whats this now?
This is Bottle. What's up?
Hey captain its someone from Earth.
- I'm not here.
- He isn't here
Tell Mr. Nasi to turn on
the answering machine.
Got it? Bottle out.
Let's go! Get ready for the hovering test.
Yes!
Your majesty we are having difficulties
contacting the Surprise.
- But you have their coordinates!
- Sure, but... we are only reaching
their mailbox
(All) What?
- What?
They're available from Monday
through Friday from 4 to 5 pm.
This can't be real, Get that crew down here!
There's not much time left!
- Aye, Sir!
- Wonder what those guys are doing.
Picking nose and swinging balls!
(Both) "Picking nose and swinging balls!"
That stops today.
From now on it's push ups and squats.
He can do that himself
Commencing hovering test.
That can't be! Those
asses won't move a bit.
Oh my, now what do we have here?
I better put this away
before the captain bags it.
- Captain, aren't we supposed to be hovering?
- Doc, why aren't we weightless?
Its no wonder!
Eating Cheesecake and chocolates all the time!
You're too fat to be weightless!
Hold on a minute.
I used to be in the hovering club!
I was the youngest ever
in the hovering marathon!
I made my license in freestyle hovering
when I was 12,
and at the age of 14 I won the Little Gold Star
at the national youth hovering contest in Swabia!
I am Hermes, messenger of the Gods!
Adieu!
- Did you know he's got cellulitis?
- Really?
- Yeah
- Where?
- In his room.
Just you wait, I'll get you!
Yes! I'm hovering!
Mr. Smock, come up here!
It's wonderful up here!
- I can't!
- He can't. C'mon, flat out, doc!
- Is that all you got?
- Geez, really
- I can't get that fat Vulcanette up.
- Hey, what's that?
- This is unacceptable!
- What's going on there?
- Geez, really!
- Hi!
- That's mine.
- Who left his roller skates lying here?
- There!
Miss Bora-Bora! Next time you'll
have a one-week ban on cheesecake!
And out with that chewing gum!
Mr. Nasi, what's the situation?
Ha, Captain!
(Nasi speaks Cantonese)
Mr Spock Did you understand
what he just said?
- Bora Bora stuck her tongue out at me!
- That's no emergency, Mr. Nasi!
Captain, there's something strange
and a little scary going on.
Someone sending an emergency signal.
But its completely unreadable
Emergency signal?
Who'd do something like that?
- Captain?
- Careful, don't get too close.
The automatic control system
shows a low sliding factor.
They use modulated pulsing vibrations...
to push through to us.
- Yeah, So?
- Shall we let them in?
Never
We can't let it get so far!
Pug speed!
Captain, with all due respect,
but pug speed's not possible right now.
- Why not?
- We have rodent damage.
- Well. Let's call it a day.
- Captain?
- What now?
I don't know what it is, but...
it's heading toward us.
Oh my, madness. What a stress!
Read it!
Red alert.
Set course for Earth
and contact the government immediately.
No way! We're in the middle of
training for the Miss Waikiki contest!
We will have to
prioritize here, right Mr. Spock?
- Ah, Captain?
- What is it?
Disobeying orders will get
your holidays cancelled.
Majesty, we recieved a reply
from the Surprise.
Finally. What do they write?
"Need something from the servo?"
What do you think
they mean with servo?
- Maybe it's a code.
- Ah! When do they get here?
We have less than an hour!
They could do it in 20 minutes
with pug speed sir.
But there's a problem your majesty.
What kind of Problem?
- Rodent damage.
Yes, I know.
I've been in treatment for a while.
I hope they don't try to beam.
It would kill them over that distance.
Get ready to beam! Activate!
Activate!
To be beamed or be beamed not
you need to be on the right spot!
Shoo!
- Ouch! Spotty, you mad?
- Mutiny!
- You'll have a single room on Honolulu!
- Geez, really! - Those things happen on Economy.
Economy? You stupid? I'm the captain!
You'll beam me on Business!
- The battery's too weak for Business.
- That beam goat probably...
- left the lights on again.
- Careful, here he comes.
Aha! Out with that!
- What is that?
- Friendship rings.
From a befriended DA.
That's all I'll say about that.
And what's in your pants?
- None of yours!
- Pants down. Pants down!
Yehes!
- Radiation protection.
- What for?
- Beaming always gets on my balls.
- Captain, I can't work like that!
Okay! But then you pay the cab!
- What is your report?
- Grab a seat, Regulator!
Madam Metapha got real crazy
boombastic plan! The plan is...
The Plan is... the plan...
Okay, I forget.
Sorry, Regulator-man, listen!
I write information on paper
and call you back later. Ok?
Walkie talkie, man!
What was that? Since when
do amateurs work for my empire?
My Regulator, that one
was a special offer at Rent-a-Spy.
Along we got this cactus for free.
I can send him back.
- Make it so. But we'll keep the cactus.
- Yes, master.
Jens, my trusty disciple.
I have a mission for you. - What?
Find out what those Earth maggots are
planning, so I can finally crush them.
Crushing! That's good!
For the beautification of our ship!
- For the beautification of our ship!
- Well, yeah, okay.
Give her something!
Thanks!
Save the whales! Find Nemo!
- Got your passport? Closed the window?
- Yes, I even closed the blinds.
I told you not to do that!
Everyone will know we're not at home!
- Arguing again?
- Go away.
- There's something on you head.
- That is my travelling hat.
- Why do you need a travelling hat?
- I'm paying the cab, so I'll come along.
- And what's that?
- That's Jutta. My reading lamp.
- It's saved my life before.
- What kind of junker is that?
- The cheapest again, huh?
- I like it.
- Who of you ordered a cab?
- Me! That was me! That was my idea!
- Who of you guys wants in the back?
- (All) Me! Me! Me!
I want the window seat!
- You cooing?
- What?
- You're cooing over him!
- No, I'm not.
- Then let him coo a little.
- Shut up and look out the window.
- So, where to?
- Earth. City of Government.
- Whoops! That'll be expensive.
- Why's that?
Right now, it'd be easier to give
someone plastic surgery during an earthquake
than to arrive there in one piece.
They're firing heavy ordnance down there.
Oh yes, life vests and parachutes
should be somewhere below that seat.
- Maybe we should get out of here?
- He's just boasting.
No problem. Just fly.
I am expected by the government.
My name is Captain Kork. Capricorn.
I am Hermes. Messenger of the Gods.
- And what is your name?
- Rock. - Soft or Hard Rock?
Grab onto something!
(All) Yes!
You can now buy duty free goods.
Anyone care for some music?
(All) Sure!
High, High, High-Ti-Tigh,
Space-Taxi to the sky.
Come on.
... My little heart...
... so hot...
... spread your legs apart...
Check it out!
... now let's start the show!
Eenie meenie miny moe!
High, High, High-Ti-Tigh,
Space-Taxi to the sky.
High, High...
What's the commotion?
Okay girls, party's over.
I'll report that one!
Spotty, keep that plate number in mind!
- Anyone got ink eraser?
- And I went to the washing bay yesterday.
Just stop it!
I'll be getting spots from all this stress!
Blow slowly, girls.
You'll get dizzy.
Okay, now we have a problem.
This is the captain. Don't mind the shaking.
We only lost our shields,
one thruster went down...
- and the plasma tank is leaking.
- I noticed that! The general condition of your...
Sit down, man!
Take the third exit at the roundabout
You are approaching the exit.
Geez, finally!
Turn right after 500 metres.
Not so good right now.
You took the wrong turn!
C'mon, baby, don't let me down!
- Could you turn off the air conditioning?
- Could you shut up for a second?
When possible please make a U turn
- Good idea!
Please wait.
Please hold the line.
You are approaching your destination.
Ensalada mista, Baby!
Don't be foolish.
Your city is completely surrounded.
My battlecookie squadron will
be ready to attack in a few minutes.
If you haven't signed the
unconditional surrender by then
I will destroy you.
It is futile. We have to surrender
while we still have a chance.
You are right. We cannot
wait any longer for the crew of the Surprise.
- That must be them.
- Heyho! Is the cheese cake ready?
Inform the queen!
- That was in style back then.
- I can't read that.
- Rock.
- Rock what?
- Rock Thats-It.
- What?
My ex-wife's name is Thats.
Mine's It. That's it.
Thank you, Mr. Thats-It.
You have been of great help to us.
What? And who'll
pay for the damage?
- A new paint job will do, I think.
- Yes! Pink Camouflage!
What? That was a 45 Space Cruiser,
a lowrider with sport suspender!
Trace elements made of Burmese titanium!
It made double speed of light
in less than 1.5 seconds!
That kind of machine cannot be painted
- in Pink Camouflage!
- Try to be sensible, Mr. Thats-It.
- Our problems are of a different nature.
- Well, I don't care about your problems!
All I care about is that
my cab is totalled because I had to
- bring you these three hoes!
- I bet he's that small.
You guys pay for the repairs
and I'm out of here. Okay?
And until that happens,
I'll just sit here, on this chair, and wait.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I could do with some coffee now.
- Chocolate?
- Nooo!
- It's bitter chocolate by Rosetto.
- It's the brand with the Rosetto-Moor.
I'm...
not ready for that.
- Who is that?
- A cab driver. We still need to pay him.
Ladies and Gentlemen...
The chairman of the
intercontinental security counsil.
Majesty!
Esteemed senators!
300 years ago,
on July 22nd, 2004 at precisely 5.35 pm,
a UFO crashed into
the desert of Nevada.
In that UFO, our scientists found
information from a galaxy far far away.
It was only with that knowledge
that we were able to colonize Mars.
We could prevent the colonization
of Mars and thus, this war,
by travelling into the year 2004
and destroying implied UFO.
But how can the UFO be completely neutralized?
With this Swiss laser!
Know a nice place to go clubbing?
- Captain?
- Yes, right, absolutely!
- That's how I would do it.
- Good. Because it's you who will be doing it.
- What? - That'll be great.
- We? No dice!
- That's totally impossible!
- We don't have time for something like that.
- We need to prepare for the Miss Waikiki contest.
- If you refuse this mission,
- there will never be a Miss Waikiki contest again.
- Bring in the time machine!
- Spotty, Smock, follow me.
- I want the window seat!
Shouldn't we tell them the
machine has never been tested?
Captain...
you are our last best hope.
- What? I'd rather send a monkey to do this.
- Animal welfare wouldn't let us.
You should put on these glasses.
Time travel is bad for your eyes.
The ignotion key will start the machine.
With these coordinates
you set destination time and place.
- Stop it or we'll leave you here!
- Confirm by pressing the green button.
This button activates a countdown.
Everything else is in this book.
Don't lose it! You'll never be able
to return without it. And don't waste energy.
- The manual!
- Spotty, travelling with you is no fun at all!
I'll get it!
The Cookie squadron launches a
large-scale attack! All exits are blocked!
We must get you to a safe place.
We have no choice. Get onto the time machine!
I'll stay here until my cab has been repaired!
Senator! There's something
you need to know!
What is it?
I forgot to pack my bra.
- Here. Take mine.
- Thank you!
It's okay.
Press the start button!
Got it!
Spotty! Heel!
Maybe I'll find a better place to sit.
- Yee, here we go!
- Spotty!
This will have serious consequences!
- What are you doing here? - I wonder, too.
- You're messing everything up!
- Does this thing have a seat heater?
- No, but I sat there just a moment ago.
Spotty is sneaking out of this again!
Now it'll be single room, definitely!
Brace yourself! Glasses on!
- I am glad to see you, Lord Shawl.
- Boot licker.
- What's that?
- Rosetto's bitter chocolate.
- It's the brand with the Rosetto-Moor.
- Thanks. Kick off.
The government building of the Earth alliance
was successfully taken over. - Excellent.
- All politicians were locked into the washhouse.
- Perfect.
- Metapha was able to escape on a time machine.
- What? How could you let that happen, asshole?
Yes. You're right. But we were able
to seize the manual of the time machine.
Goooood.
I'm going to make a phone call.
Wow!
- It actually worked!
- Unbelievable.
- Now we can...
- Prevent my wedding! - What?
- We could see Elvis live!
- The end of the world is near
- and you think of Elvis?
- I dreamed of football just now.
I dreamed I was a pastry cook and
shaped a quarterback from marzipan.
I stuck a lucky coin on top of it
and put it into the shop window next to the tarts.
- What country did you enter?
- I didn't enter anything.
- Captain! Get up! Look, a pony!
- Where are we?
A petting zoo!
- Dammit!
- Oh my! Rowdies everywhere!
July 22nd, 1304. A short miss.
- Neat thing you got us into.
- I didn't do anything.
Then maybe you should do something now.
Keep cool, princess.
We'll be gone in a second.
Dear Romans! We came from
the future to save the world!
Smocky, take a picture.
Say cheeese cake!
Witchcraft! Catch them!
I'm out of here!
- Who is he?
-Who?
- He!
- Ah, I see.
Who is he?
Speak, you sleazy son of a bitch!
- What did you do to the woman?
Now tell me, Is he of noble blood?
My name is Til Schweiger, and
I make my living as an actor.
It's not much, but it's enough for
two weeks of vacation in a year.
And what do you do all day long,
throne farter?
Mylord, he is a liar. This
man is certainly not an actor.
But he has got guts. I was
told he was a remarkable fighter.
An important tournament takes
place tomorrow. My honor is at stake,
but my best horseman was
overrun by a Crusade last week. Nasty thing.
- How about putting up danger signs?
- Do we have danger signs?
No, Sire, but the virgin Adrea
has some spare crosses.
- Yes! Put up Adrea's Crosses!
- Hey, great idea! Can I go now?
It is his fault my
subsitute fell from his horse.
Hence, he will have to win
the tournament for me tomorrow.
If he does, he is free. If he doesn't,
he and his entourage will be hanged
and the woman will be mine.
Cheers!
But Sire! Only those of noble blood
may take part in the tournaments!
That's right.
Hereby I knight you Sire of
of Behynde.
Those Pigs travelled to the past to
eradicate our existence.
This is bad news.
Well, yes. Sure
But I also have good news for you.
Go ahead.
This book contains a
time machine construction manual.
- I turned my moped into one.
- And? Does it work?
Like you wouldn't believe, master!
Here is the proof. I just
got tomorrow's newspaper.
Regulator snatches the earth.
Four eyes bludgeoned with frying pan for treason.
Poor pig
- They won't write about me.
- For this to come true
you have to stop them!
Can you trace their route?
Sure. I'll sniff them
out with my sniff radar.
- Jens!
- Master?
There is something you need to know.
What?
Roughly 30 years ago
a baby came along.
Without sock and without shoe.
And that, dear Jens, that was you.
You lost me, my Regulator.
I... am... your father!
Sure thing Daddy. You can count on me.
cyanara!
By the way, the Lady's dress
suits you remarkably well.
She wore it just yesterday
while being busy with the jester.
- You have a wife? - I had.
- Where is she now?
- Hanging outside.
- You hanged her outside? Why?
For the lack of indoor gallows.
- Two pizzas No. 33 for William the Endmost!
- To the Knight of Behynde!
Say, what is your star sign?
Well, your zodiac.
- You do have a zodiac, don't you?
- Well, yes... Virgo.
- A virgin!
- A virgin? Where? Finally! Bring her here!
I want one, too! Here first!
I was here before him! Shut up!
- Virgo goes wonderfully with Butterfly.
- That's no zodiac.
Yes, it is. In the Vulcanette
horoscope. I am a Butterfly.
We only have insects for zodiacs.
House Fly, Tse Tse Fly,
Blowfly, Mayfly...
or the Wasp!
- Want to see my ascendant?
- No, keep it where it is.
- Save that for your boyfriend.
- What? He's not my boyfriend.
He's just my captain.
He'd get lost without me all the time.
- Besides, he has no idea what women want.
- Neither do I. You have to be handsome...
Beauty is not that important.
What you need is humor.
I have! A doctor tells his patient
"I have good news and bad news."
"Good: You have one day to live."
"Bad: I forgot to tell you..."
"yesterday."
Forgot... yesterday...
Not bad.
Do you want to know the magical
question that sets every woman's heart on fire?
Want to go shopping?
Shopping? And I always thought
women liked men who play the piano.
Baby, I'm strollin' on top of the sky.
Why don't you, don't you, don't you,
Baby, come along with me?
Why don't you come along with me?
I don't think I will ever
marry. I wouldn't, at that.
Neither would I anymore.
My ex-wife took everything.
My house, my dog, my job...
even my hole puncher.
Oh my, now you can't even file anything away!
Oh well. Let me show you something. Here.
My little pink pal is the only thing left.
Oh, you little piggy you!
Say, can I touch it?
Of course.
- Oh my, it's all shrivelled up!
- Well, it's been in there for a while.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- Come, push it.
- I'd like to have one myself.
- Come on, push it harder.
My, where is it? My, what's
it doing? My, there it is!
- I don't want to make it burst.
- It won't. My dog used to chew on it.
The joust: two knights try to push each
other off the horse with a lance.
If your friend goes down,
he loses and we will be married by tonight.
I don't think you two
would make a good couple.
- What's wrong?
- Well, how did we sleep last night?
- I didn't get a wink of sleep.
- Yes, I imagine.
- What's that on your foot?
- A shoe.
- Where did you get that from?
- My room mate had his leg hacked off
for no apparent reason.
I felt sorry and bought his shoe.
- Shut up, you witches!
- Your the witch
Dear Lords, dear Ladys,
dear mob!
Our dearest patronizing host, who is
delighted to see you all have come here...
Duke William the Endmost of Shareholding!
Dear Lords, dear Ladys!
Sir Further-Winston-Fattenberry of
West Firstwhistle-Minster-Shatwood Castle,
Third Count of Yorkshire Forest
Wooden-Lancester-Puddingham...
Not Puddingham It's Pettingham, you idiot!
Ah... oh... Right.
Sir Further-Winston-Fattenberry of
West Firstwhistle-Minster-Shatwood Castle,
Third Count of Yorkshire Forest
Wooden-Lancester-Pettingham,
Sir Richard Carsharing,
can not be with us today.
(Crowd) aaaaaaawwwwwwwwwwww
Well well, the plague.
Stepping into the breach...
the mysterious Black Knight!
Competing against him, under
the crest of Duke William...
the Sassy Sire of Behynde!
I worked on that outfit all night.
But it was worth it.
Loose screw, huh?
- Jens Shawl!
- Jawohl.
I will beat the Sassy Sire for you.
Faster you sow
- You have to cancel the tournament!
- Too late.
In case you care at all, I don't feel well.
I have to go bisi-bisi since last night,
but they don't even have toilet paper here.
Calm you sow!
- You need to raise your lance, Rocky!
- There. You're cooing. You said "Rocky"!
If the Black Knight wins we're all doomed!
- It's not the end of the world.
- You have no idea!
Jawohl!
- I can't take it much longer!
- Neither can I. Too bad about that outfit!
My bladder is about to explode
and you act like a halibut in the heat!
Rock!
- Didn't hurt at all.
- Think about our future!
Don't worry, princess.
Let me handle this.
He could as well resign.
Your bosom will be mine!
I'll rather go and puke
then let you touch me, Duke.
Put your Lanze in the air,
and rock it like you just don't care!
Everybody say, oh yeahl
Oh yeah!
They asked me how I knew
My true love was true.
I of course replied,
"Something here inside
cannot be denied."
Jawohl! Yes! Jawohl!
Yes! We're getting married!
Where's the priest?
Hey, don't touch! Hands off! Heh!
- What are you planning?
- Some little fireworks for our wedding.
I know how you feel.
I fell from the bunk bed when I was a kid.
Excuse me! He's lying on top of my bladder.
Hey, wait!
What?
Oh Willy!
Do you want to make me happy?
Yeah, definitely!
Jawohl! Higher you pigs!
- I'm ready, Willy-Boy!
- Good! Move a little together, my dear!
They're getting away!
Let me down, assholes!
What a picture!
Stop it!
- Come on baby, where's the cheese cake?
- In here!
Cheeeeese cake!
Oh crap.
- They're gone!
- William's a sorcerer.
Well, burn him!
Now I'll go and meet my Lord
because of that bosom I adored.
- What happened?
- You were unconscious. We're there.
- Hey! Hey, stop pulling!
- Wishi-wishi, bisi-bisi
- Well, look!
- Oh thank God!
- C'mon, hurry, will ya?
- Yeah. Look, someone forgot his pants in here.
- Heave ho!
- Man, this is heavy!
That armoire goes up to the bedroom.
Be careful! These are the
furniture of our new sheriff.
- It all has to be perfect tomorrow.
- Sure, mayor.
Oh, do be careful!
I dreamed of soccer just now.
I was a quarterback made of marzipan.
Someone stuck a lucky coin to my head and
put me into the shop window next to the tarts.
- Who was that?
- Some gay pastry cook.
Whoa whoa whoa!
- And where are the others?
- Piddling.
That was close. I wouldn't even wish
Bora-Bora such a full bladder.
Shouldn't have had all that asparagus.
Well, how do you like it?
- This outfit is so totally old fashioned.
- Poppycock and fiddlesticks!
- We won't stand out in this national costume.
- You're jingling.
I have a world to save!
Watch me, this is how you move in Nevada.
Shoulders up, swing your hips.
Think of Johnny Weir
and don't forget your breathing!
Try it!
Forget it!
Ah, fresh asparagus soup!
It's still warm!
- Smocky.
- Leave me alone.
- How far is it to the ground?
- I don't know.
- Well, please look.
- I can't.
- This is the right place, but we're in the wrong time.
- Can you repair the time machine?
- Not without the manual.
- What do we do now?
First of all, find the girls.
Strange. I can't get rid of the feeling...
- they're somewhere around here.
- Last warning, Smock!
- How far is it to the ground?
- Forget it! - Are we being mutinous?
- That Rock guy is a bad influence for you!
- You're just being jealous!
- Be careful, will you!
- Hey. The princess is worrying about me.
- What do you mean?
- Well, if a woman worries about a man...
- I'm worrying about our mission!
- And I'm worried about my cab and my money.
What?
- But we're stuck here without the time machine!
- You should have been more careful.
- Oh, so it's my fault now?
- I couldn't I was unconscious.
- That's so typical!
You're a jealous gratin!
You'll look down now, or I'll tell
Mr. Rock that you have a green testicle!
You're such a bully!
- I took the rap for you, Lady!
- And who kicked that leather lump into my face?
If it wasn't for me, you'd be
a juicy steak at the stake!
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- What? - So you don't.
I'll tell you something. You like me.
- This is not about you! Got it?
- Excuse me, can I get my sports section back?
- Mayor Roony!
- That's all wrong!
- More to the left!
- Mayor Roony!
A telegraph from Roswell! It's horrible!
God be with us!
The former sheriff...
isn't cold and stiff yet,
and they're already coming back to town!
They're on the 12 o'clock train.
They're back!
- You have your mother's pulpy porridge butt!
- Travelling with you is no fun at all!
- I'm never taking you along again!
- So what? There are plenty of people
- who'd love to take me along!
- Who? That Rock-bottom maybe?
Yeah! Our knees touched,
and I got the feeling he
wanted it too! Stop smirking!
Maybe I'll go to
- Mykonos with him next year!
- I'm not giving you a holiday.
Sheriff Shorty? Ah, I thought
you'd arrive tomorrow. Anyway. Good luck!
And you're bigger than I expected!
- And which one is the sheriff?
- The one with the star, Jim.
- Then I'll go and save the world without you!
- Ha, you can't!
- Yes I can. - No you can't.
- Yes I can.
- I don't believe this.
- No you can't. I have the Swiss laser!
You sly Vulcanette cow!
- Hey, are you batty?
- I believe Shorty was shorter last time we met him.
Well, it's been what, 10 years?
He could have grown.
Dammit!
Game over!
Daddy will be delighted!
He's got a moped!
Oh no, not again.
Crap!
What's wrong?
Get a grip, asshole!
John, you hold the sheriff off my back.
Jim, wash your hands and go inside.
Sorry, John.
I can't stay outside to play.
Don't worry. I found two new friends already.
- Shoes! - Yes, boss.
- John, you have ten minutes.
We have a pub to sell
to the Apaches later today.
- We are from the...
- People Village!
- We are peace-loving Village People.
- Ladies and Seoritas!
>From Medicine Bow, Wyoming,
it's your host for tonight: Mr. Santa Maria!
- Isn't he gorgeous?
- I'm your biggest fan!
Welcome to "The Santa Show"!
Our guest for today is Jim.
Hello, Jim.
- What did you bring us there, Jim?
- Rheuma blankets, boss.
Isn't that wonderful?
Schnuffi-Puffi...
Buy one, get one freel
Schnuffi-Puffi!
Schnuffi-Puffi,
and your wild ride's going on!
Now on sale!
- I think he's cooing over you.
- Really?
C'mon! Draw!
- What?
- Your pistol.
It's his first time!
Geez, thanks!
- I can't get it out!
- Now you see what it's like.
- Are you alright, captain?
- Yes, but...
- Where's Rock?
- I'm really getting tired of hearing that name!
Who of you ordered a cab?
- Thank God, there he is!
- "Thank God, there he is!"
- You are a real hero!
- I know.
- But we don't drink champagne.
- The chief of the Apaches does.
- Oh look! Someone's lying there!
- Yes, that's my John.
My Regulator.
Your shuttle to Earth is ready.
- Has Lord Shawl reported in yet?
- No, my Regulator!
But we captured this man.
He pretended to be mowing the lawn.
He actually is part of the crew
that managed to flee with the time machine.
Interesting. I'm sure he can tell
us something about their plans.
I'm not saying anything!
I've already lost my reading lamp to this war!
- It can't get worse, can it!
- Then there is nothing I can do for you.
You fool!
Hermes!
Commence a press release:
High treason! Spectacle wearer...
- slain with a pan.
- Aye, my Regulator.
We have conquered Earth.
The Era of Darkness shall begin.
- I think this is our exit!
- I don't know how to slow this thing down!
Jump off!
- Great! Now I got sand in my ears!
- No surprise, your ears are quite ample.
- Are you alright, princess?
- I think so.
Better.
That's our sofa!
Why is it smouldering?
What are you doing with our sofa?
It's not a toy, you know!
Now look how that looks!
It's so totally wrecked!
Do you even know who I am?
My name is Juergen Thorsten Kork,
captain of the Traumschiff Surprise.
I have the responsibility for this sofa
as well as for a crew of over 40 men.
And it's not always easy to make ends meet!
He repaired the time sofa!
Your turn!
Okay!
You...
You again.
- What is that?
- A corkscrew.
A magnifying glass.
No!
Your time is up!
The UFO!
Time to say goodbye, french fry.
Rock!
Want to...
Want to go shopping?
Yes I do!
- See! Your time to coo is over, Smocky.
- I can still keep him on the back burner.
- There is something you have to know.
- What is it?
I...
- I really suck when it comes to sex.
- Oh Rock! So do I!
- Gee, what a cute thingy!
- Careful, Smock, it might bite.
Maybe I'll talk to him.
- Hello, stranger!
- Huh?
You friend or foe?
- Ah!
- A friend!
- Oh, I think the poor thing has catched a cold.
- Wait a sec.
You're a really good boy, aren't you?
- Look, now you broke it! You dumb cow!
- That's not enough, I'm afraid.
- We did it!
- That's all? This will change the future?
Even small things can have a big effect.
I don't know about you, but
I'm really homesick now.
- Yes!
- I wonder what awaits us at home.
- Hopefully a fresh cheese cake
in Honolulu, right, Smocky?
- There's not enough energy. Overload.
- Overload?
- We're too heavy. - What?
- We'll make 200 years, tops.
- We're 76.375 kg overweight.
- Oh no!
- How much are you?
- 54 kg.
- My beach weight's 75 kg.
- I'm 73. - What about you, Smocky?
Well, how much is it?
76 kilo and 375 grams.
Smocky?
Groans was right.
I'm just a fat Vulcanette.
Thanks for everything.
They found us.
Take this. Whenever you're lonely,
just press it.
Don't go!
- You have to go now.
- How could I, without you?
- I'll stay with you.
- No, you have to win the Miss Waikiki contest.
Smocky!
I'll always be with you, captain.
You're the bravest Vulcanette in the world!
Farewell!
Gotta run.
And you expect us to believe that story?
So you are a time traveller.
And you came from the year 2304
to save the world.
What do you think, Mr. Oilfield?
- Sir, he's telling the truth.
- Are you sure, Mr. Cornfield?
- Yes, Mr. Wheatfield. The lie
detector confirms it. He can fool us
- but he can't fool the machine.
- Please, Mrs. Ricefield.
Mr. Smock. Your story sounds truly...
- unbelievable.
- Geez, really.
But can you prove to us
that you are from the future?
- What the hell is that?
- Oh geez, I had forgotten about that!
I've never seen anything like it!
- It vibrates when it gets hot.
- Yes, General.
- A clinical thermometer with vibration.
- That's proof.
This man does indeed come from the future.
What is that?
Surprise!
- Welcome home, captain!
- What?
This is impossible....
You were just... I mean... you were...
- Why are you here?
- Well, you never believed me, did you!
Galapagos turtle!
Yesterday was my 335th birthday!
Three...! You haven't changed a bit!
No grey hair...
- no cellulite in your face! Nothing!
- Yes. Wasn't cheap though.
So you... waited for me for 300 years?
Yes. But I made good use of that time.
Isn't it beautiful?
How did you do that?
I sold our cheese cake recipe
to McDonald's.
Captain's log no. 1 of our
Traumschiff Surprise, Captain Kork.
Saved the world once more.
By destroying the UFO in 2004
we changed the future.
Mars was never colonized,
and Mr. Smock has refurbished
Earth during the last 300 years.
Now nothing can stop us!
'Cause we're so pretty
and so canny and so slim and so slender
We'll be Miss Waikiki!
And shower to the left!
And shower to the right!
And don't forget the soap!
One more time!
And five, six, seven, eight
Five, six, seven, eight
And touch and push!
And towel to the left!
And towel to the right!
And don't forget the willy!
Dry the willy to the beat!
You can count on me, daddy.
I'm a Vulcanette vulgaris.
We can be up to 400 years old because we are
a type of Galapapago...
I'm a...
This thing farts!
Sure. I'll snaff them
out with my snaffledidap.
Yes!
- Klaus Kinski?
- Yes. I'm hovering. Come up.
Sure, Dad. Shoe
can count on me.... shshshsh...
- I am Hermes, messenger of the Gods.
- And whahamaminib?
They travelled to the past to
erararara...
Rrrrrr! Rrrrrr!
I miss my moped.
- I used to be on the hovering club!
- On?
I made my license in freestyle hovering
when I washwei... shwe....
shwiba... hi there!
...when I was 12,
and I won the Federal Cross of Merit
at the national youth hovering con...
- Federal Cross?
- Put that pipe away!
- I am Hermes, messenger of the Gods!
High, High, High-Ti-Tigh,
Space-Taxi to the sky.
Come on.
... My little heart...
... so hot...
... spread your legs apart...
Check it out!
... now let's start the show!
Eenie meenie miny moe!
High, High, High-Ti-Tigh,
Space-Taxi to the sky.
I...
- I forgot to pack my bra.
- Here.
Take m...
William is a sorcerer!
Sorry, mouth full.
Do you want to make me happy?
Yes, definitely!
My nose went up!
Sir Further-Winston-Fattenberry of
West Firstwhistle-Minster-Shatwood Castle,
Third Count of... Fuck!
Fuck, hey!
There are plenty of people who'd lovuff...
There are plenty of people who'd lovuff... sorry!
There are plenty...
Do you even know who I am?
I am Captain Juergen Thorsten Kork from the
Planet of the Apes. Sorry.
Bring me a Quattro staggioni, okay?
And turn that stupid music off.
Now, be honest, Smocky.
Didn't you get incredibly bored
without me during the last 300 years?
Oh well, I had a little lie-in...
- visited my relatives
- That's nice.
- I did my tax return.
- Yes, that's important.
And then I won bronze...
at the Olympic Games of 2068
in the ladies team showering.
Oh, really! Our Smocky has
always been an ace, hasn't he?
- What's up, Spotty?
- Captain, I beamed someone up.
- He wants to join in with us!
- Send him up. He'll get some cheese cake, too!
Aye aye, my captain!
Well, who could it be!
Come in!
- Servus!
- Voil! Anyone need a pearl diver?
Fascinating.